I was woken up early by my body and was
watching extinction rebellion YouTube
video which I loved the extinction
rebellion I think that a massive global
movement to demand action from our
governments is the best course of action
that we have access to intellectually
that we get that that it's kind of
what's been done in the past and and
it's the best option we have for the
masses right now however I don't think
it's the best option I think that we
need to think outside of the box and
instead of demanding our governments
create citizen assemblies that then they
have to listen to even if the citizens
assembly destroys our life destroys our
economic system and which is less
important than our planet but still
important I still want food in the
supermarket I still wanna be able to eat
and so on access to healthcare and
transportation and our governments are
not designed to have the rapid solutions
that we need to implement solutions as
they create chaos what would be designed
to do that is a technological system
that's designed to do that having
different people who want to work on
various issues able to work on them and
as they have ripple effects on every
other industry and problem we're dealing
with that as it comes there's enough of
us on this planet who care and enough of
us on this planet who can brainstorm
solutions including solutions to all of
the issues that we create by creating
solutions so we are going to create our
technology company it is owned
cooperatively run cooperatively run for
cooperation and for purpose instead of
competition and profit if Google wanted
to solve the world's problems they have
the money they have the people they
could create it even if they were going
to create it which spoiler alert they're
never going to we wouldn't trust it we
can create it and we can take over from
Google eventually and take over from
Facebook
we are the ones that give them our power
we're their commodity if we create a
cooperative it solves those same issues
that we go to them to solve getting
access to information with Google
getting access to people with Facebook
and getting access to goods with Amazon
we can do all three of those in a
cooperative format where the profits not
going to shareholders that profit is
remaining and getting used for purpose
we can create the systems that feed the
masses that don't rely on NGOs and don't
rely on or Geo's that are a massive
cooperative that runs efficiently and
effectively and yet nobody has to give
up their power there are their own
individual power we just keep asking how
can we help how can we create a food
system that feeds the masses ethically
and it won't be one option
it'll be dozens and dozens of options
that work together efficiently so you
get to choose which one you're part of
which one do you want to give your time
and energy to which one meets your needs
which one can you help improve none of
them how do we help you create your own
that you can do that with and we
systematically tackle every single
industry make sure our transportation
needs are met understand the supply
chain and then recreate it understand
the complexity of the issues that are on
their planet that nobody currently
understands because you can't it cannot
be held in one human brain it has to be
us working collectively and we don't
need everyone those that wanted to be in
the penet of system can remain in the
competitive system until it's no longer
there because we've out competed it
working cooperatively gives us massive
innovation because we don't need a
patent system we it's open source we
allow people to build on what we created
before for our own benefit and the
benefit of humanity
all we have to do is create it and we
its massive what we're going to create
but it starts with us creating the
platform to hold a conversation to vote
on issues to form groups and actually
work with them
social media designed for change
designed to bring you together with
people that believe in what you believe
in and actually have a create a solution
that isn't pouring out into the streets
and demanding our governments create
solutions that they have no idea how to
create they're just as overwhelmed as we
are and they're working in their own
self-interest which is their money
depends on the system being in effect
come on use clean air I really need to
retire eventually and my hundreds of
millions dollars I'm going to cut it we
have to meet people where they are and
we have to create the solutions that
start from where we are as a planet and
then all of it can be done rapidly when
we have open source science we all can
participate in when instead of of giving
our you know taking a snapshot of our
meal and posting that on Instagram still
do that what if when you did that you
helped other people create better food
you helped other people get the
nutritional information you helped
create an efficient entire supply chain
simply by doing as easy of actions on
social medias you're currently doing
that's how easy we need it to be and it
will be that easy because some of us
don't want it to be that easy we want
the hard work and we'll do the hard work
to make it that easy and we're
continually listening for what makes it
easy what makes it fun it doesn't need
to be one size fits all but it does
behind-the-scenes need to be everyone's
actions adding into the pool everyone's
data adding into the pool that they
retain control over because that's the
only way they're gonna want to get there
their data we can create solutions to
all of it in fact it's the only way to
do it because one thing leads into
everything else
it affects all the other industries we
don't need our governments to give us a
citizen's assembly we can just make the
technology that makes that an ongoing
daily event globally
and invites people to the table to have
a conversation no behind closed doors no
I get to have a conversation and you
don't get to be part of the conversation
because you weren't selected everyone's
invited to the table everyone gets to
bring their ideas and they don't get a
monopoly is it and we're already at six
and a half minutes so I can't get into
how we do that but I'm always open to
questions in the comments and since I'm
doing a daily video if you ask a good
one it will generate a entire video I
will see you tomorrow
please like and subscribe we are going
to create the global technological
cooperative it turns this all around it
starts with me and grows to a tiny group
of us that have the skills to reach the
masses
take care